Guide to the Mabel Dodge Luhan Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Scrapbooks, 1912-1949; Series IV; 21.25; (17 boxes)
  - Untitled, 1914-28, n.d. (Box 98, Folder 2267)
    Articles: "Mabel Dodge Writes About the Liver and Liver Trouble" ["Next to the Mothers..."] "Orientalism Comes West on East's Power" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Fear and Its Results" "Choose Idol, then Love Him Forever" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Three Kinds of People" "Mabel Dodge Writes About More Light in the Home" "Mabel Dodge Writes About the Crime of Stealing Energy" "Men and Girls Spend All Energy Well" "Mabel Dodge Writes Abouth Three Young Men in a Pool" "Mabel Dodge Writes on the Growth of Love" "Fear, Brutal Parasite Feeds Out Soul Till it Dies" "Mabel Dodge Tells About the Unconscious" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Looking Ahead" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Mothers" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Quilts" "The Secret of War" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Adopting a Baby" "Consuming Energy is Keeping Well" "Taos Solves the H.C. of L. for Many of Us" "Mabel Dodge Writes About the Pivotal Man" "Man's History in Architecture" "Mabel Dodge's Article on 'Pass'd! for Us, Forever Pass'd" "Mabel Dodge Writes About Robert Edmond Jones" "Mabel Dodge Says Love's Gentle..." "Love is a Big Energy Dynamo" "Mabel Dodge Writes About Your Faculty of Attention" "Mabel Dodge's Article" "Los Santos de Nuevo Mexico" "Who Wants Pictures?" "Mabel Dodge Talks About a Corner in the Hills" "Mabel Dodge Talks About the In-Between Times" "Mabel Dodge Writes on Working for a Living"
- Personal Papers, 1906-1959; Series V; 1.25; (3 boxes)
  Series III, Personal Papers, is organized into ten subseries: Artwork, Clippings, Diaries, Financial and Legal Records, Invitations and Announcements, John Evans Papers, Medical Records, Postcards, Printed Ephemera, and Other.
  - ARTWORK
    - Guimar de Angulo drawing, n.d.
    - John [GeeCurley?] drawing, 1922 Jul (Box 99, Folder 2268)
    - Marsden Hartley painting, [ca. 1910-11] (Box Art, Folder 2269)
    - Stephen Haweis painting, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2270)
    - Bradford Johnson lithograph, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2271)
    - [Robert Edmond Jones?] painting (Box Art, Folder 2272)
    - Gisella Lacher painting, n.d.
    - D. H. Lawrence drawings, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2273)
    - D. H. Lawrence watercolor, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2274)
    - Maurice Sterne drawings, 1918-19, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2275)
    - Max Weber painting, 1911 (Box Art, Folder 2276)
    - Unidentified, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2277)
  - CLIPPINGS
    - Brief mentions, 1917-51, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2278-2281)
    - General interest
      - Literary references, 1932-59, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2285-2289)
      - Photographs and pictures, 1916-38, n.d. (Box Art, Folder 2290)
  - DIARIES
    - Diary, holograph, 1916, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2291-2292)
    - Diary, typescript and typescript carbon, 1946 Aug, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2293)
    - Diary, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2294)
  - FINANCIAL AND LEGAL RECORDS
    - Bills and receipts, [1931?]-42 (Box 100, Folder 2295)
    - Contracts, 1929-45 (Box 100, Folder 2296)
    - Documents on Native American Indians, 1943 (Box 100, Folder 2297)
    - Royalty statements, 1930-43 (Box 100, Folder 2298)
  - INVITATIONS AND ANNOUNCEMENTS
    - Appearances by Mabel Dodge Luhan, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2299)
    - Other events, 1913-52, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2300)
  - JOHN EVANS PAPERS
    - Drawings, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2301)
    - Morristown School report, 1916 Nov 8 (Box 100, Folder 2302)
    - Separation Agreement and Property Settlement, 1933 Jul 21 (Box 100, Folder 2303)
    - Sketchbook of drawings and watercolors, 1906 (Box 100, Folder 2304)
  - MEDICAL RECORDS
    - Patient form completed in holograph, 1916 Jan 3 (Box 100, Folder 2305)
    - [Smith Ely Jelliffe's?] notebook on MDL's analysis, 1916 (Box 100, Folder 2306)
  - POSTCARDS
    - People
      - Native American Indians (Box 100, Folder 2307-2308)
      - Stokowski, Leopold, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2309)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2310)
    - Places
      - Belgrade, Hungary, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2311)
      - Church at Gratchanitsa, Kosovo, Serbia, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2312)
      - Hayground windmill at Watermill, Long Island, New York (Box 100, Folder 2313)
      - Hyde Park Hotel, London, England (Box 100, Folder 2314)
      - Lone Pine, California, and Mt. Whitney (Box 100, Folder 2315)
      - Los Angeles, California, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2316)
      - Mexico, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2317)
      - Native American Indian sites in Southwest, 1917-20, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 2318)
      - [New Mexico?], n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2319)
      - Nuuanu Pali, Oahu, Hawaii, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2320)
      - Poppi, Italy, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2321)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2322)
    - Other
      - Artwork, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2323)
      - Elephant, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2324)
      - International Exhibition of Modern Art, 1913 (Box 101, Folder 2325)
  - PRINTED EPHEMERA
    - Brochures, pamphlets and promotional material, 1936-44, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2326)
    - Calling and thank you cards, 1952, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2327)
    - Exhibition catalogs and lists, 1916-30, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2328)
    - Material regarding Native American Indians (Box 101, Folder 2329)
    - Obituaries and tributes, 1917-36 (Box 101, Folder 2330)
    - Periodicals, 1938-46, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2331)
    - Programs for concerts, conferences and theatrical events, 1943-52, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2332)
    - Publicity for books, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2333)
    - Reproductions of photographs, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2334)
    - Sales catalogs, 1938-39 (Box 101, Folder 2335)
  - OTHER
    - Astrological notes, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2336)
    - Author's file completed in holograph for New Mexico Quarterly, 1950 Nov (Box 101, Folder 2337)
    - Beverly Hills Hotel and Bungalows stamp booklet (Box 101, Folder 2338)
    - Calendar, 1950 (Box 101, Folder 2339)
    - Certificate of Divorce, 1917 May 15 (Box 101, Folder 2340)
    - Drawing of house plans, 1930 Apr 29 (Box 101, Folder 2341)
    - Drawings of Holy Cross Hospital, Taos, 1951, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2342)
    - Ex Libris stamp, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2343)
    - Holograph and typescript excerpts (Box 101, Folder 2344)
    - Holograph draft for I.W.W. pageant, [1913] (Box 101, Folder 2345)
    - Holograph draft of topics for presentation to Industrial Relations Commission, 1916 Mar 19 (Box 101, Folder 2346)
    - Lecture course ticket for Mary Austin's "How to Develop Your Genius", n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2347)
    - List of Georgia O'Keeffe paintings, 1930 (Box 101, Folder 2348)
    - [Empty folder], n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2349)
    - Material regarding sale of "Big House", 1945, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2350)
    - Membership cards, 1939, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2351)
    - Minutes for unidentified committee meeting in MDL's hand, 1914 Jan 14 (Box 101, Folder 2352)
    - Miscellaneous notes in MDL's hand (Box 101, Folder 2353)
    - Monogram for Mabel Dodge Luhan, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2354)
    - New York World's Fair 1939 certificate
    - Notebook of quotations in MDL's hand (Box 101, Folder 2355)
    - "Notes for celebrating the two artists..."] in MDL's hand (Box 101, Folder 2356)
    - Order form for The Jones Leather Company, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2357)
    - Printed cartoon by Will Shuster, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2358)
    - Las Programas de Taos constitution, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2359)
    - Recipe for "claret [leup?]", n.d. (Box 101, Folder 2360)
    - Synopsis of Gabriele D'Annunzio's Gioconda (Box 101, Folder 2361)
    - University of Maryland Basic Program class schedule, 1945 Jan (Box 101, Folder 2362)
- Subject Files, 1915-1961; Series VI; 0.42; (1 box)
  Series V, Subject Files, is organized into two subseries: People and Topics.
  - PEOPLE
    - Adrian, Gilbert; Gaynor, Janet, 1939, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 2363)
    - Bragdon, Claude Fayette, 1946, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2364)
    - Brand, Donald D. (Donald Dilworth) (Box 102, Folder 2365)
    - Brett, Dorothy, 1944, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2366)
    - Brisbane, Alice, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2367)
    - Cary family, 1917-41, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2368-2369)
    - Collier, John, [1936] (Box 102, Folder 2370)
    - Cook family, 1933, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2371)
    - Dasburg, Andrew, 1948 Oct 28 (Box 102, Folder 2372)
    - Donahoe, Edward, 1945, 1952 (Box 102, Folder 2373)
    - Duncan, Isadora, 1921, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2374)
    - Eloesser, Leo, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2375)
    - Evans family, 1933-47, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2376)
    - Feshin, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1961 Mar 12 (Box 102, Folder 2377)
    - Hamlin, Mrs. Chauncey J., 1933, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2378)
    - Hapgood, Hutchins, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2379)
    - Herbert, Xavier, 1943 May 10 (Box 102, Folder 2380)
    - Highet, Gilbert, 1952, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2381)
    - Jeffers, Robinson, 1946 Apr 21 (Box 102, Folder 2382)
    - Jones, Robert Edmond, 1945-46, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2383)
    - Kiker, Henry A., n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2384)
    - Lawrence, D. H. (David Herbert), 1939-44, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2385)
    - Lawrence, Frieda von Richthofen, 1956, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2386)
    - Luhan, Tony, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2387)
    - Mauldin, Bill, 1947 Oct (Box 102, Folder 2388)
    - Pickrell, Donald G., n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2389)
    - Rogers, Millicent, 1953, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2390)
    - Rumsey family, 1927, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2391)
    - Skinner, Cornelia Otis, 1938-39, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2392)
    - Stein, Gertrude, 1946 Nov 24 (Box 102, Folder 2393)
    - Sterne, Maurice, 1917-57, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2394)
    - Stokowski, Leopold, 1944-45 (Box 102, Folder 2395)
    - Taylor, Mrs. Henry Fitch, 1921 Nov 10 (Box 102, Folder 2396)
    - Toomer, Jean, 1940, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2397)
    - Tregor, Nison, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2398)
    - Van Vechten, Carl, 1926-29, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2399)
    - Vanderbilt, Willian H. (William Henry) (Box 102, Folder 2400)
    - Others, 1927-36, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2401)
  - TOPICS
    - Buffalo, New York, 1928-32 (Box 102, Folder 2402)
    - New Mexico, 1936-51, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2403-2404)
    - Polo, 1938, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2405)
    - Other, 1917-54, n.d. (Box 102, Folder 2406)
- 2011 Addition, 1942-1942; Series VII; 1; (1 box)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred from Sterling Memorial Library, Cataloging and Metadata Services Department, date unknown.
  Series VII. 2011 Addition contains printing materials relating to Luhan's books projects, Lorenzo in Taos and Winter in Taos. There is a plate shipping crate and record for Lorenzo in Taos and two printing plates, including the title page and first page, for and shipping labels for Winter in Taos.
  - Lorenzo in Taos
    - Shipping crate, 1942 Sep 30 (Box 113)
    - Plate shipping record, 1942 Sep 30 (Box 113)
  - Winter in Taos
    - Printing plates, Sage Books edition, n.d.; 2 (Box 113)
    - Shipping labels, 1942, n.d. (Box 113)
- Oversize, 7.36; (5 boxes)
  - Letter from Dorothy Brett to Mabel Dodge Luhan (In Series I), 1948 Jan 31 (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2407)
  - Letter from Malvina Hoffman to Mabel Dodge Luhan (In Series I), 1934 (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2408)
  - Letters from Gisella Lacher to Mabel Dodge Luhan (In Series I), 1936-51, n.d. (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2409)
  - Printed version of "Isadora Duncan" (In Series II), 1936 Jul (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2410)
  - Printed version of "On the Career and Character of Katharine Cornell" (In Series II), 1923 Jul (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2411)
  - Printed version of "The Mirror" (In Series II), n.d. (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2412)
  - Poem, "Yellow," by "Spud" Johnson printed by Laughing Horse Press (In Series II), 1924 Dec (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2413)
  - Galley for "The First Lady Chatterley" by D. H. Lawrence (In Series II), 1944 (Box 103 (Oversize), folder 2414)
  - Galley for "A Modern Lover" by D. H. Lawrence (In Series II), n.d. (Box 103 (Oversize), folder 2415)
  - Article by Joe Alex Morris in The Saturday Evening Post (In Series II), 1950 Jul 22 (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2416)
  - Page from manuscript, "The Colorado Man," by John Reed (In Series II), [1914?] (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2417)
  - Article by John B. Sanchez (In Series II) (Box 103 (Oversize), Folder 2418)
  - Photographs of MDL with John Evans (In Series III), [1916?] (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2419)
  - Photographs of MDL with Tony Luhan (In Series III), 1949 May (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2420)
  - Portrait of MDL by Associated Press (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2421)
  - Studio portraits of MDL by Hall (In Series III), [1890s] (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2422)
  - Portraits of MDL by Russell Lynes (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2423)
  - Portrait of Tony Luhan by Ansel Adams (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2424)
  - Photograph of Tony Luhan (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2425)
  - Photographs of Tony Luhan with John Evans (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2426)
  - Studio portrait of "Grandma" Cook (In Series III) (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2427)
  - Studio portraits of Alice Henderson Evans and children (In Series III) (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2428)
  - Photographs of John Evans (In Series III), 1915, n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2429)
  - Photographs of John Evans and family (In Series III) (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2430)
  - Photograph of Evans girls (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2431)
  - Studio portrait of Carlos de Heredia (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2432)
  - Studio portraits of Sara Cook Ganson Montague (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2433)
  - Photograph of unidentified family (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2434)
  - Portraits of Gilbert Adrian (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2435)
  - Portrait of Janet Adrian (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2436)
  - Photograph of Bayard Boyesen (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2437)
  - Photograph of Arthur Brisbane (In Series III), n.d. (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2438)
  - Photograph of John Collier Jr. (In Series III), 1939 (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2439)
  - Photograph of Andrew Dasburg (In Series III) (Box 104 (Oversize), Folder 2440)
  - Photograph of Isadora Duncan (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2441)
  - Photograph of Georges Ivanovitch Gurdjieff (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2442)
  - Photograph of Robinson Jeffers by Edward Weston (In Series III), 1929-1930 (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2442a)
  - Studio portrait of Arch Kepner (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2443)
  - Photograph of Arthur Lee (In Series III), 1910 (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2444)
  - Photograph of Arthur N. Levine (In Series III), 1939 Jun 14 (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2445)
  - Photograph of Walter Lippmann (In Series III), 1915 Nov 27 (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2446)
  - Photograph of Lincoln Steffens (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2447)
  - Photographs of Maurice Sterne (In Series III), 1917, n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2448)
  - Studio portrait of Evangeline Stokowska (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2449)
  - Photograph of Nison Tregor and Tryanovsky (In Series III) (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2450)
  - Photograph of First Inter-American Congress with Lázaro Cárdenas (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2451)
  - Photographs of unidentified people (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2452)
  - Photograph of unidentified Native American Indian man (In Series III) (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2453)
  - Photograph of unidentified Native American Indian men (In Series III) (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2454)
  - Mounted Photographs Folder [4] (In Series III), n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2455)
  - Mounted Photographs Folder [5] (In Series III), 1917-21, n.d. (Box 105 (Oversize), Folder 2456)
  - Mounted Photographs Folder [6] (In Series III), n.d. (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2457)
  - Photographs of Villa Curonia, Florence (In Series III), n.d. (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2458)
  - Photograph of 23 Washington Square apartment interior, New York (In Series III), 1916 (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2459)
  - Photographs of Los Gallos, Taos (In Series III), n.d. (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2460)
  - Photograph of Twining Canyon by Laura Gilpin (In Series III), [1948?] (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2461)
  - Photograph of bust of Knute Rockne by Nison Tregor (In Series III), n.d. (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2462)
  - Photograph of unidentified artwork (In Series III), n.d. (Box 106 (Oversize), Folder 2463)
  - Guimar de Angulo drawing (In Series V), n.d. (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2464)
  - Gisella Lacher painting (In Series V), n.d. (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2465)
  - Clippings on MDL of general interest F.3 (In Series V), 1949-51 (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2466)
  - New York World's Fair certificate (In Series V), 1939 (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2467)
  - Clipping on Cary family (In Series VI), 1917 Jul 15 (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2468)
  - Section of Taos Star (In Series VI), 1949 Dec 22 (Box 107 (Oversize), Folder 2469)
- Restricted Papers, 0.42; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until 2020. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Restricted (Box 108, Folder 2470)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.83; (2 boxes)
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 2 (Box 109, Folder 2471)
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 109, Folder 2472)
  - Box 1, folder 16 (Box 109, Folder 2473)
  - Box 1, folder 17 (Box 109, Folder 2474)
  - Box 1, folder 18 (Box 109, Folder 2475)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 109, Folder 2476)
  - Box 1, folder 35 (Box 109, Folder 2477)
  - Box 1, folder 36 (Box 109, Folder 2478)
  - Box 2, folder 46 (Box 109, Folder 2479)
  - Box 2, folder 53 (Box 109, Folder 2480)
  - Box 2, folder 56 (Box 109, Folder 2481)
  - Box 2, folder 72 (Box 109, Folder 2482)
  - Box 3, folder 74 (Box 109, Folder 2483)
  - Box 3, folder 95 (Box 109, Folder 2484)
  - Box 3, folder 99 (Box 109, Folder 2485)
  - Box 4, folder 106 (Box 109, Folder 2486)
  - Box 4, folder 111 (Box 109, Folder 2487)
  - Box 4, folder 116 (Box 109, Folder 2488)
  - Box 4, folder 118 (Box 109, Folder 2489)
  - Box 4, folder 119 (Box 109, Folder 2490)
  - Box 4, folder 126 (Box 109, Folder 2491)
  - Box 5, folder 131 (Box 109, Folder 2492)
  - Box 5, folder 139 (Box 109, Folder 2493)
  - Box 5, folder 145 (Box 109, Folder 2494)
  - Box 5, folder 147 (Box 109, Folder 2495)
  - Box 5, folder 148 (Box 109, Folder 2496)
  - Box 5, folder 150 (Box 109, Folder 2497)
  - Box 5, folder 152 (Box 109, Folder 2498)
  - Box 6, folder 181 (Box 109, Folder 2499)
  - Box 7, folder 195 (Box 109, Folder 2500)
  - Box 7, folder 201 (Box 109, Folder 2501)
  - Box 7, folder 202 (Box 109, Folder 2502)
  - Box 7, folder 207 (Box 109, Folder 2503)
  - Box 7, folder 218 (Box 109, Folder 2504)
  - Box 7, folder 219 (Box 109, Folder 2505)
  - Box 7, folder 221 (Box 109, Folder 2506)
  - Box 8, folder 239 (Box 109, Folder 2507)
  - Box 8, folder 241 (Box 109, Folder 2508)
  - Box 8, folder 248 (Box 109, Folder 2509)
  - Box 8, folder 249 (Box 109, Folder 2510)
  - Box 9, folder 253 (Box 109, Folder 2511)
  - Box 9, folder 255 (Box 109, Folder 2512)
  - Box 9, folder 258 (Box 109, Folder 2513)
  - Box 9, folder 259 (Box 109, Folder 2514)
  - Box 10, folder 272 (Box 109, Folder 2515)
  - Box 10, folder 276 (Box 109, Folder 2516)
  - Box 10, folder 279 (Box 109, Folder 2517)
  - Box 10, folder 282 (Box 109, Folder 2518)
  - Box 10, folder 283 (Box 109, Folder 2519)
  - Box 10, folder 285 (Box 109, Folder 2520)
  - Box 10, folder 292 (Box 109, Folder 2521)
  - Box 10, folder 295 (Box 109, Folder 2522)
  - Box 11, folder 319 (Box 109, Folder 2523)
  - Box 12, folder 325 (Box 109, Folder 2524)
  - Box 12, folder 326 (Box 109, Folder 2525)
  - Box 12, folder 332 (Box 109, Folder 2526)
  - Box 12, folder 334 (Box 109, Folder 2527)
  - Box 12, folder 341 (Box 109, Folder 2528)
  - Box 13, folder 342 (Box 109, Folder 2529)
  - Box 13, folder 345 (Box 109, Folder 2530)
  - Box 13, folder 347 (Box 109, Folder 2531)
  - Box 13, folder 350 (Box 109, Folder 2532)
  - Box 13, folder 354 (Box 109, Folder 2533)
  - Box 14, folder 360 (Box 109, Folder 2534)
  - Box 14, folder 364 (Box 109, Folder 2535)
  - Box 14, folder 365 (Box 109, Folder 2536)
  - Box 14, folder 367 (Box 109, Folder 2537)
  - Box 15, folder 395 (Box 109, Folder 2538)
  - Box 15, folder 411 (Box 109, Folder 2539)
  - Box 16, folder 433 (Box 109, Folder 2540)
  - Box 16, folder 434 (Box 109, Folder 2541)
  - Box 16, folder 437 (Box 109, Folder 2542)
  - Box 16, folder 439 (Box 109, Folder 2543)
  - Box 16, folder 458 (Box 109, Folder 2544)
  - Box 16, folder 459 (Box 109, Folder 2545)
  - Box 17, folder 462 (Box 109, Folder 2546)
  - Box 17, folder 463 (Box 109, Folder 2547)
  - Box 17, folder 466 (Box 109, Folder 2548)
  - Box 17, folder 469 (Box 109, Folder 2549)
  - Box 18, folder 486 (Box 109, Folder 2550)
  - Box 18, folder 492 (Box 109, Folder 2551)
  - Box 18, folder 494 (Box 109, Folder 2552)
  - Box 18, folder 501 (Box 109, Folder 2553)
  - Box 18, folder 508 (Box 109, Folder 2554)
  - Box 18, folder 510 (Box 109, Folder 2555)
  - Box 19, folder 537 (Box 109, Folder 2556)
  - Box 19, folder 544 (Box 109, Folder 2557)
  - Box 20, folder 549 (Box 109, Folder 2558)
  - Box 20, folder 550 (Box 109, Folder 2559)
  - Box 20, folder 552 (Box 109, Folder 2560)
  - Box 20, folder 557 (Box 109, Folder 2561)
  - Box 20, folder 561 (Box 109, Folder 2562)
  - Box 21, folder 584 (Box 109, Folder 2563)
  - Box 21, folder 591 (Box 109, Folder 2564)
  - Box 22, folder 609 (Box 109, Folder 2565)
  - Box 23, folder 641 (Box 110, Folder 2566)
  - Box 23, folder 655 (Box 110, Folder 2567)
  - Box 24, folder 659 (Box 110, Folder 2568)
  - Box 24, folder 667 (Box 110, Folder 2569)
  - Box 24, folder 668 (Box 110, Folder 2570)
  - Box 24, folder 675 (Box 110, Folder 2571)
  - Box 24, folder 676 (Box 110, Folder 2572)
  - Box 24, folder 677 (Box 110, Folder 2573)
  - Box 25, folder 691 (Box 110, Folder 2574)
  - Box 25, folder 692 (Box 110, Folder 2575)
  - Box 25, folder 704 (Box 110, Folder 2576)
  - Box 25, folder 714 (Box 110, Folder 2577)
  - Box 26, folder 721 (Box 110, Folder 2578)
  - Box 26, folder 746 (Box 110, Folder 2579)
  - Box 26, folder 747 (Box 110, Folder 2580)
  - Box 26, folder 751 (Box 110, Folder 2581)
  - Box 26, folder 752 (Box 110, Folder 2582)
  - Box 27, folder 753 (Box 110, Folder 2583)
  - Box 27, folder 771 (Box 110, Folder 2584)
  - Box 27, folder 778 (Box 110, Folder 2585)
  - Box 27, folder 779 (Box 110, Folder 2586)
  - Box 28, folder 792 (Box 110, Folder 2587)
  - Box 28, folder 798 (Box 110, Folder 2588)
  - Box 28, folder 812 (Box 110, Folder 2589)
  - Box 28, folder 829 (Box 110, Folder 2590)
  - Box 29, folder 833 (Box 110, Folder 2591)
  - Box 29, folder 834 (Box 110, Folder 2592)
  - Box 29, folder 837 (Box 110, Folder 2593)
  - Box 29, folder 839 (Box 110, Folder 2594)
  - Box 29, folder 844 (Box 110, Folder 2595)
  - Box 29, folder 845 (Box 110, Folder 2596)
  - Box 29, folder 846 (Box 110, Folder 2597)
  - Box 29, folder 848 (Box 110, Folder 2598)
  - Box 30, folder 854 (Box 110, Folder 2599)
  - Box 30, folder 856 (Box 110, Folder 2600)
  - Box 30, folder 862 (Box 110, Folder 2601)
  - Box 30, folder 864 (Box 110, Folder 2602)
  - Box 30, folder 866 (Box 110, Folder 2603)
  - Box 30, folder 880 (Box 110, Folder 2604)
  - Box 31, folder 897 (Box 110, Folder 2605)